

# **About**

I'm a professionally trained cook (also experienced in restaurant reception) but my focus is on the deep studies of computer science and blockchain technologies.

I also teach physics and mathematics to High School students as a freelancer.

I'm a car owner with driving license.

### Education

🔾 2022 - 2023 🖪 **CYBERSECURITY SPECIALIZATION** 

Google, Mountain View, United States

2022 - 2023 🖪 **DATA SCIENCE SPECIALIZATION** 

IBM, New York, United States

2019 - in progress...

**BACHELOR OF PHYSICS** 

Università degli Studi di Milano Bicocca, Milan, Italy

2012 - 2018 HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA OF

IPSEOA Carlo Porta, Milan, Italy

# 🕰 Languages

**HOSPITALITY** 

**ITALIAN** 

**ENGLISH** 

**SPANISH** 



## Contact



<u> Cinisello Balsamo, Milan, Italy</u>



+39 3454860367



maurizio.falconi47@gmail.com



/MaurizioFalconi

# Maurizio Falconi

### Jr Full Stack Developer

I collected lots of working experiences in hospitality field, therefore i chose to cut it off some from my resume, due to my working goal purposes.

If you are interested to check it out my full working experience, skills and certifications you can visit falker47/gituhub.io/myresume

Note: when it appears the icon 🖪 next to an activity you can click on it to see the certification. Every underlined text has its relative link.

### **Freelance Activity**

January 2023 - present

#### **Private STEM Teacher**

I'm teaching physics and mathematics to High School students as a freelancer. I'm following **10+ students** with a current average of **25h** of lessons **per week**. You can reach my Teacher Accounts on <u>LeTueLezioni</u> and <u>SuperProf</u> to check my students reviews, or my site that I developed on my own

### **Working Experience**

February 2023 - June 2023

MasterZ | Strada della Repubblica 97, 43121 Parma, Italy



### **BLOCKCHAIN & DIGITAL ASSETS ACADEMY ATTENDEE**

Winner of the scholarship for the 5th edition of the training course by AIO Blockchain Lab. The following skills I learned, were put into practice in the development of a final project work, evaluated among the Top 50 of the entire course:

- Blockchain Technologies, Smart Contracts, Digital Assets (CBDC and crypto)
- DeFi, DApps, Centralized and Decentralized Exchanges

#### March 2023 - April 2023

Blazar Group | Via Besso 27, 6900 Lugano, Switzerland



Full-time training course (*with project work*) where I learned and implemented:

- C#, Azure, MSSQL for backend solutions
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, Angular for frontend solutions
- . GitHub and Trello for the entire project task management

#### October 2021 - February 2023

MU Fish \ Via Galileo Galilei 5, Nova Milanese (MB), Italy

### **COMMIS de RANG**

Part-time work where I was in charge of:

- · Reception of the restaurant customers
- Booking Management
- Waiting service

### November 2017 - January 2022

Da Vittorio srl | Brusaporto (BG), Italy

#### 4th LEVEL CHEF

Job on call in occasion of important events where I was in charge of:

- Execution and Plating of Da Vittorio most famous dishes
- · Cooking Line Preparation
- · Contact with the Public

